既然我们已经在Android manifest.xml中同步了weather provider进程
Now that we've registered our weather provider in the Android manifest,
我们就可以来编写天气插件了
it's time to begin coding our weather provider.
这是实现内容提供的过程中最终也是最关键的一步
This is the final and most involved step in implementing our content provider.
我们即将着手完成内容提供的核心功能
We'll be filling out these core content provider functions.
除了我们已经完成的onCreate函数
Except for onCreate, which we've already done for
我们也已经为数据库助手添加了实例变量
you, we've added an instance variable for our data base helper.
我们在onCreate中初始化上述功能
We initialize this in our onCreate function.
并会在大部分的内容提供方法下使用数据库助手
We will use this database helper in most of the content provider methods.
我们先来看看内容提供方法里的getType方法
The first of the content provider methods that we will look at is getType.
对我们的app来说实现getType的功能版本
Implementing the functional version of getType isn't strictly necessary for
并非严格需要
our application.
但这是一个非常好的方法来回顾我们即将着手的URI
But it's a nice way to review what uris we're planning to handle.
我们已经完成了部分getType的功能
We partially filled out the getType function for you.
我们使用之前建立的urimatchr工具类来匹配传入的uri
We use the urimatcher we built earlier to match the given uri
这和之前所做的是不同的
against the expressions we've compiled in.
每次匹配都会返回在WeatherContract中定义的类型
For each match, we return the types that we've defined in the weather contract.
谨记  要传达的关键信息是content uri是否
Remember that the key information that this conveys, is weather the content uri
返回一个包含单一记录的item类型的数据库cursor
will be returning a database cursor containing a single record type item, or
还是包含多个记录的directory类型
multiple records type directory.
除了数据库cursor  内容提供商也可以用来返回
Content providers can also be used to return other kinds of data
其他类型的数据
than just database cursors.
比如说  如果我们想要内容提供商以content uri返回一个JEPG图像
For example, if we wanted the content provider to return JPEG images for
我们应该用这个函数返回标准的mime类型
a content uri, we would have this function return the standard mime type,
即image/jpeg
image/jpeg.
接下来我们来谈谈TestProvider中testGetType方法
Let's un comment the testGetType test from within TestProvider.
这为我们接下来的工作做了准备
This will get us ready for the next coding exercise.